alldevotion.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy - Official Human, LLC

##### Last Updated January 24, 2012

This website (whether a standalone website, or an application running on a social network) is operated by Official Human, LLC.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to tell you how we will use any personal data you provide through this website. Please read it carefully.

## What We Collect

We collect information about your interaction with our website that is required to make the website work for you. For example, we may collect the votes you have cast or the content you have seen or which friends you invited.

When you access our website through a social network (such as Facebook), we may also collect all personal information that the social network sends to us and that we are allowed to keep under the Terms of Service of the social network. For example, we may collect your user id or your name or your gender.

We collect all personal information you voluntarily provide to us. Some of this information is not required for you to use our website, and when prompted you will have an option to decline the submission. Other such information is required to enable certain parts of the website, for example if you wish to receive updates via email or sms, you will need to tell us your email or phone number.

When you make purchases on our website, we also collect transaction information. _We do not collect your bank or credit card details_.

We collect aggregate information for the purposes of tracking website usage, in order to help us improve our website, and for research and analysis purposes. The aggregate information does not, however, include details that can be used to identify you. This aggregate information includes internet protocol addresses, browser types, browser languages, referring / exit pages and URLs, other browser history, platform types, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time.

## User Submitted Content

Some parts of our website accept user generated content. Such content is considered public. We may make it available for syndication to other websites, or for indexing to search engines.

## How We Use Your Information

We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties.

The information we collect about you is used to improve the content of our website; used to customize the content and/or layout of our website for you; used to notify you about updates to our website; shared with agents, services or contractors who assist in providing support for our internal operations; used by us to contact you for marketing purposes; disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website.

## Transfer of Information

In the event that the business is sold or integrated with another business, your details will be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchaser's adviser and will be passed to the new owners of the business.

## Third Party Advertising

We do not provide any personal information about you to third-party advertisers. We may, however, use your personal information to target adverts on our website to you. For example this could include advertisements designed for your age group, or your gender.

Third-party advertisers may use technologies such as cookies, pixel tags and beacons to help target, manage and optimize their adverts. We have no access or control over technologies used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

## Cookies

When you access our website we may send a cookie to your computer. A cookie is a small text file recorded on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user and contains certain information about your use of the website.

We use the cookie to improve the quality of our website, to tailor the content to you, to make the website easier for you to use, to make recommendations for you.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may be unable to use all or parts of our website if cookies are disabled.

Find out how to disable / enable cookies by looking at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

## Links

Our website may contain links to other websites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you choose to browse from our website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other websites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

## How We Store Your Information

We have implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

## Controlling Your Personal Information

You can terminate your account at any time which will remove your personal information from view by other users. We may however, at our discretion, keep information about you that is on our systems following your termination.

## Accessing and Updating Your Information

You may, if you wish, see the information we hold about you. To do so please contact us at the email provided below in section Contacting Us. We may require you to provide a proof of identity and to pay an administration fee (currently $10) to provide a copy of the information we hold. Please note that in certain circumstances we may withhold access to your information where we have the legal right to do so.

You may update your personal information at any time by contacting us at the email provided below in section Contacting Us.

## Updates to This Privacy Policy

If our privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at
